{
    "questions_and_answers": [
        {
            "subject": "ComfyUI_GMIC",
            "question": "How is G'MIC a part of ComfyUI?",
            "answer": "G'MIC in ComfyUI is a custom node that provides image-processing features, including effects, filtering, geometric manipulation, image data, and color."
        },
        {
            "subject": "ComfyUI_GMIC",
            "question": "What makes G'MIC friendly for users?",
            "answer": "G'MIC in ComfyUI is designed to be user-friendly for both beginners and power users with its ongoing documented workflows."
        },
        {
            "subject": "ComfyUI_GMIC",
            "question": "What is the command to install the G'MIC custom node?",
            "answer": "You can install the G'MIC custom node by cloning the repository with the command `git clone https://github.com/gemell1/ComfyUI_GMIC` or by copying the `comfy_gmic.py` file to your custom nodes folder."
        },
        {
            "subject": "ComfyUI_GMIC",
            "question": "What is required to use the G'MIC custom node?",
            "answer": "To use the G'MIC custom node, you need to download the G'MIC Command-line interface (CLI) and G'MIC-Qt stand-alone interface, put the executable path in your PATH, and drag the provided workflow to ComfyUI."
        },
        {
            "subject": "ComfyUI_GMIC",
            "question": "When was the first upload of the G'MIC custom node for ComfyUI?",
            "answer": "The first upload of the G'MIC custom node for ComfyUI was in November."
        },
        {
            "subject": "ComfyUI_GMIC",
            "question": "What platforms does the G'MIC custom node support?",
            "answer": "The G'MIC custom node supports better cross-platform functionality as of February."
        },
        {
            "subject": "ComfyUI_GMIC",
            "question": "Is there a breaking change to be aware of in March?",
            "answer": "Yes, in March there were breaking changes, and it is recommended to recreate your workflow."
        },
        {
            "subject": "ComfyUI_GMIC",
            "question": "What is the version of G'MIC-Qt and CLI used in the testing?",
            "answer": "The version of G'MIC-Qt and CLI used in the testing is 3.3.4."
        },
        {
            "subject": "ComfyUI_GMIC",
            "question": "What version of ComfyUI is G'MIC custom node tested on?",
            "answer": "The G'MIC custom node is tested on ComfyUI version [March 09](https://github.com/comfyanonymous/ComfyUI/tree/a9ee9589b72aa0e2931f1c0705524c56adaee26d)."
        },
        {
            "subject": "ComfyUI_GMIC",
            "question": "Where can I find more ComfyUI custom nodes for image processing?",
            "answer": "You can find more ComfyUI custom nodes for image processing by visiting the [link](https://github.com/gemell1/ComfyUI_GMIC/wiki)."
        }
    ]
}